db = {
    "suits": [{
    question: `Harvey Specter is considered one of New York's most brilliant corporate litigation lawyers, but what's his unusual middle name?
    (a) Michael
    (b) Reginald
    (c) Brandon
    `,
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: `Which partner loves mudding and had a cat named Bruno?
    (a) Harvey Specter
    (b) Louis Litt
    (c) Jessica Pearson
    `,
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: `Which English lawyer described Donna Paulsen as having \"a body like Elizabeth Hurley and the sass of a Maggie Thatcher\" in season 3?
    (a) Michael Ross
    (b) Harvey Specter
    (c) Stephen Huntley
    `,
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: `Where did Harvey Specter work before he became an associate at Pearson Hardman?
    (a) New York District Attorney's Office
    (b) Bratton Gould
    (c) Darby International
    `,
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: `Jessica Pearson and Daniel Hardman ousted three named partners in order to create Pearson Hardman. What was the firm called before the ousting?
    (a) Specter Zane Litt
    (b) Gordon Schmidt Van Dyke
    (c) Pearson Hardman
    `,
    answer: "b",
  },
  ],
  "siliconvalley": [{
    question: `Silicon Valley Q1
    (a) Michael
    (b) Reginald
    (c) Brandon
    `,
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: `Which partner loves mudding and had a cat named Bruno?
    (a) Harvey Specter
    (b) Louis Litt
    (c) Jessica Pearson
    `,
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: `Which English lawyer described Donna Paulsen as having \"a body like Elizabeth Hurley and the sass of a Maggie Thatcher\" in season 3?
    (a) Michael Ross
    (b) Harvey Specter
    (c) Stephen Huntley
    `,
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    question: `Where did Harvey Specter work before he became an associate at Pearson Hardman?
    (a) New York District Attorney's Office
    (b) Bratton Gould
    (c) Darby International
    `,
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    question: `Jessica Pearson and Daniel Hardman ousted three named partners in order to create Pearson Hardman. What was the firm called before the ousting?
    (a) Specter Zane Litt
    (b) Gordon Schmidt Van Dyke
    (c) Pearson Hardman
    `,
    answer: "b",
  },
  ]
}